{
    "id": "a9dd406f6a3a49e98c26107fda15516b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The villagers are steeped ............................... ignorance and superstition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Their customs are similar to ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Solomon succeeded .................................. the throne of David.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am suspicious ................................ his true intentions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He tampered ................................ the office files.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can testify ............................. his honesty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ............................... reminding him about this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He touched ................................ unemployment and allied problems in his speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "upon",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Be always true .................................... your conscience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is wanting ................................... sympathy and understanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}